<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Your awesome title</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:03:05 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:03:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>V + Y Wedding</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;
On May 25th, 2017, on our 6 year anniversary,  Vincent and I exchanged vows. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The morning started with me doing my hair and makeup at home.  Yes, I did it myself! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some would say, &quot;Omg I could never&quot; but your girl was determined to come out looking radiant AF! My everyday makeup is already fairly minimal. So doing a big glam look just didn&#39;t feel right for me. I still wanted to look like myself with an extra side of &quot;Damnnnn, girl you lookin&#39; good&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/hair_makeup.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did research the entire time I was engaged to see what foundation would work best with my skin type. I found what blushes had the best longevity. And what combination of eyeshadows I liked based on everyday wear. In the end, I assembled a bridal beauty arsenal. The three months before the wedding I practiced every single weekend and made sure to nail down the timing as well. That way I could do my makeup at a good pace, no problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s what I used that day:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skincare&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mask:&lt;/b&gt; Tony Moly I&#39;m Real Makgeolli Mask Sheet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Serum:&lt;/b&gt; Innisfree Green Tea Seed Serum&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Face Oil:&lt;/b&gt; Khiel&#39;s Daily Reviving Concentrate&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Moisturizer:&lt;/b&gt; Kiehl&#39;s Ultra Facial Cream&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Makeup&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Primer:&lt;/b&gt; Clio Kill Cover Moist Tone Up Primer &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Highlighting drops:&lt;/b&gt; Algenist Reveal Concentrated Lumizing Drops in Pearl&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Foundation:&lt;/b&gt; Make Up For Ever Ultra HD Invisible Cover Foundation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Concealer:&lt;/b&gt; A&#39;PIEU Moist Creamy Concealer &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Powder foundation:&lt;/b&gt; TOO FACED Cocoa Powder Foundation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cream blush:&lt;/b&gt; H&amp;amp;M Cream Blusher in Sunny Peach&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Powder blush:&lt;/b&gt; TOO FACED Love Flush Long-Lasting 16-Hour Blush in &quot;I Will Always Love You&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bronzer/Contour:&lt;/b&gt; TOO FACED Chocolate Soleil Matte Bronzer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cheek Highlight:&lt;/b&gt; Stila All Over Shimmer Duo in Kitten&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lipstick:&lt;/b&gt; CHANEL ROUGE COCO SHINE in Boy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lip Liner:&lt;/b&gt; Mac Lip Pencil in Subculture&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lip tint:&lt;/b&gt; Peripera Ink Velvet in #8 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lip gloss:&lt;/b&gt; TOO FACED Sweet Peach Creamy Lip Oil in Pure Peach&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lashes:&lt;/b&gt; Etude House Volume #2 lashes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Eyebrows:&lt;/b&gt; Innisfree Eco Eyebrow Pencil in #2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Eyeshadows:&lt;/b&gt; MAC Stroke of Midnight Eyeshadow Palette&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for hair, I knew I wanted really soft waves, so that was very easy to pull off.  I purchased a curling iron off of Amazon and practiced, practiced, practiced as much as I could. The day of, I set everything with the OUAI wave spray and the OUAI medium hair spray.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/dress.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did not want to spend an arm and a leg on my wedding dress. I was wrapping my head around a look I wanted and I ended up ordering a beautiful gown online only to receive an email saying the dress was out of stock. Just my luck. So I continued my search for a couple more months with no success. Thankfully everything came together once I stumbled upon this dress. It was airy, simple and beautiful. Coming in at $179, I was instantly sold. It was way below my original budget! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/shoes.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My gray strappy heels I got at Nordstrom months back really came through on my wedding day. These were well broken in and at a comfortable heel height which proved to be crucial. It was raining heavily that day and needed shoes that were reliable so I wouldn&#39;t slip but were still really cute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/bouquet.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our amazing friend Nicole is a talented AF floral designer. She followed her dreams and now has a kick ass business, Still Event &amp;amp; Design, making the most beautiful arrangements. Nicole is an inspiration. With just one phone call and a few emails, she knew exactly what I was looking for.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time I was getting ready, Vincent was at the Envision hotel. If you&#39;re in the greater Boston area or are going to be soon, check it out. It recently opened in spring 2017 and is super nice.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/vincent_tie.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His tie...HIS TIE! We found this at our local Nordstrom and knew it was the one. So lovely, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/bout.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vincent opted for a navy blue custom made suit from Indochino. The color really makes the boutineer pop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our ceremony took place at an event space right in the heart of Seaport District in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We managed to take a couple of &quot;first look&quot; photos before the ceremony started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/kiss.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/black_white.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ceremony itself was perfect. Short and sweet. We went for traditional vows since I knew if we were to write our own no one would have understood what I was saying over the sounds of me breathing and heavy crying. Who am I kidding? I cried regardless, lol. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/ceremony.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After our vows, we took some more quick pics with our friends and family, notably our little baby girl, Cammy. Have you been to a wedding before that had a kitty? Yeah. We are cat people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/cammy.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/lil_family.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/y_family.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/v_family.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next stop was our lunch reception! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/toro_menu.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/toro_drink.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The folks over at Toro were so flexible and accommodating to our party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/big_table.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The food was amazing, like always. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/paella_2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of a cake, we went the cupcake route. Georgetown cupcakes are always a home run!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/cupcake_closeup.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/cupcakes.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wedding/cupcake_kiss.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I learned from being a bride:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Being engaged is fucking awesome. Enjoy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vincent and I were engaged for a year and a half before we actually got married. In that time we focused on making our little apartment our home. A place where we can’t wait to come back after work and unwind. We traveled all the way to Seoul. Then months later to Toronto. We spent a lot of time just being together and in a way getting to know one another in different circumstances. I fell in love with him all over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Set a budget and stick to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I live by one rule when it comes to money. “If I can’t buy it now, I’m not buying it. Period. Not putting it on a credit card. If I really want it, I’ll save for it.” And that didn’t change when it came to my wedding. Vincent and I spent a good amount of time saving up for the wedding and honeymoon. Having a tangible amount as a goal to save up for really helped me set a budget weekly and it was easy to stick to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) This is YOUR wedding. Not anyone else’s. Do what makes you happy as a couple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because we wanted to keep the wedding small we knew we had to make some tough decisions. There were times where I would second guess my choices but I had to stop and think back to the reason we wanted a small wedding in the first place. I learned that there’s no right or wrong when it comes to weddings. We kept the ceremony small. But we’re still planning to throw a party to celebrate with more friends and family later on to mark our 100 days of marriage. Ultimately because we wanted to pay for everything, it was OUR decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do what feels right for you. Don’t want bridesmaids? Cool. Want to treat your guests to a  7-course meal? Sure! Want a kid free wedding? By all means. No one should be stopping you on what you want on your wedding day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Remember, your wedding is only one day out of an entire lifetime together. Try not to stress it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is an enormous pressure but on couples on their wedding day. That stress can feel so crushing at times. But to put it in perspective, it is just one day. Sure it’s a special day, but you have an entire lifetime ahead to share with our significant other. If one thing goes wrong, that’s ok. Keep your cool. At the very least it will add character to your wedding when you tell your grandkids the story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Share your plans with friends and family once things are finalized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Originally I had so many plans for my wedding. I wanted a destination wedding. Then things changed. And it happens…a lot! I wish I kept my mouth closed and waited until I had concrete plans and details to share with family. But parents are so curious to know what’s going on that I thought just adding the words “we were thinking about maybe…” would clarify that my wedding was still in the planning stage but no. Wrap up the key points and then share the info.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Have a backup plan. Then a backup plan for that backup plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there’s anything I learned, it’s that the universe really likes to play tricks on me, SO I HAVE TO COME CORRECT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vincent and I originally had outdoor wedding plans. Three days before our big day we knew we had to bring the ceremony indoors. While we scrambled to find a venue, one of my vendors got sick and needed surgery and was not going to be at the wedding. The day before the wedding I got a call from Toro that their electricity needed to be shut off for 24 hours due to maintenance and that they might not be able to host us. On top of that, I had hit my head so hard on a glass fixture the night before by accident that I was starting to get a bruise on my forehead. IT WAS A FUCKING MESS, OK?! But because we kept the wedding small, I felt I could still handle it. I couldn’t imagine having all those issues happening on a bigger scale without having a huge emotional breakdown. I learned that I need to have a backup plan for every scenario. And then another backup plan for that, just in case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Take the day before your wedding off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, this is a big one. I thought, “Yeah I’m literally having 15 guests. The wedding is so small. I don’t need a day off to plan beforehand.” I was so wrong. The day before my wedding was rough. I STILL WENT TO WORK because I was going on my honeymoon the next day after my wedding and had things to wrap up. I was going through a lot that day (see point 6 above) and on top of that I still needed to pick up the cupcakes, do my nails, my at home facial, I needed to give Cammy Cat a bath, clean the apartment, eat and sleep.  There are not enough hours in the day. I ended up sleeping for about two hours that night and feeling really lethargic on my wedding day. It also didn’t help that I couldn’t eat a thing because of the nerves. Take the day before your wedding off. Heck, do two days before the wedding if you can. Your body will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phew, hope that advice helps at least one of you out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before this post is over I just want to say a huge thank you to our families, our friends, our vendors and everyone who’s sent their best wishes over to Vincent and I. We really appreciate it and it means so much to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vendors:
Flowers: Still Event Design 
Photos: Peter Lazzarino Photography
Video: Daymian Mejia
Wedding dress: Lulus (https://www.lulus.com/products/bariano-ocean-of-elegance-ivory-maxi-dress/225650.html?gclid=EAIaIQobChMIl6f_2d2H1QIVmYSzCh0AWwugEAQYASABEgK1YvD_BwE)
Bride Shoes: Charles David
Groom Suit: Indochino
Groom Tie: Nordstrom
Groom Shoes: Johnson + Murphy 
Ceremony Venue: breather
Reception Lunch: Toro
Cupcakes: Georgetown Cupcakes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
  (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i[&#39;GoogleAnalyticsObject&#39;]=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
  (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
  m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
  })(window,document,&#39;script&#39;,&#39;https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js&#39;,&#39;ga&#39;);

  ga(&#39;create&#39;, &#39;UA-87732213-1&#39;, &#39;auto&#39;);
  ga(&#39;send&#39;, &#39;pageview&#39;);

&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2017/07/13/wedding.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2017/07/13/wedding.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Japan, Korea and Birthday Hauls</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;
As Lil&#39; Kim would say, &quot;I&#39;ve been gone for a minute now I&#39;m back with the jump off&quot;. I had a wedding (post about that coming soon) and honeymoon to plan and execute. But I&#39;m here and ready to spill the tea on my beauty buys! There&#39;s a lot of stuff I picked up abroad on my honeymoon tour but I also splurged a little in the last week becasue why not treat &#39;yo self on your birthday? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Japan&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Muji:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/muji.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
Muji High Moisturizing Milk Lotion / Muji Cleansing Oil / Muji High Moisturizing Toning Water Toner / Muji Milk Cleanser / Muji All In One Essence / Muji Compressed Facial Mask Sheets&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wouldn&#39;t say that my skin is necessarily sensitive but this line came highly recommended by a friend. I use this whole line at night as a base for my skincare routine and it&#39;s really soothing. The oil cleanser is the star of the show. I even like it better than the Tatcha cleansing oil. The essence has a gel consistency that is excellent as well. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muji also carries little face mask capsules that when submerged in essences, ampoules or serums they expand and turn into a full sized sheet mask. Perfect for traveling or when you have extra essences laying around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Don Quijote --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Don Quijote:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/donki.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
Nivea Sun Protect Super Water Gel SPF 50+++ / DHC Lip Cream / Kose Lip Gel Magic / Rohto C3 Cube Aqua Charge Eye Drops / Silicone Sponge / Shiseido Senka Perfect Whip Cleansing Foam
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Nivea sunscreen is flat out amazing. It&#39;s not streaky, lightweight and easy to apply. Western sunscreens need to step up their game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; I&#39;m also really liking the DHC lip balm. It&#39;s thick enough to apply lots of moisture to your lips without feeling overly sticky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Kose Lip Gel Magic balm was something I bought out of impulse. It promised to keep your lipstick on hours after eating, drinking...etc. It definitely extends the wear of your lipstick but I haven&#39;t used it enough to see how long it truly lasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/eye_drops.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Japanese eye drops are on a whole new level. I even saw some slightly yellow tinted eyedrops to help combat the blue light from electronic devices...What a time to be alive, folks. I got the C3 eyedrops because of some great reviews online and I was totally sold on the cute and simple packaging. It makes wearing contacts actually enjoyable for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Silicone sponges are all over Instagram and I caved into the hype. I like to apply my foundation all over with this and then go in with some fine detail work with a disposable foam sponge. Two thumbs up for ease of cleanliness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Perfect Whip cleanser was advertised literally everywhere I went. Apparently, it&#39;s the number one best seller in Japan. And for good reason. A rich lather, delicate scent and squeaky clean feel without completely stripping your skin, color me impressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Daiso + It&#39;s Demo --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Daiso + It&#39;s Demo:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/daiso.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
Daiso Impact Eyelashes #07 / Daiso Makeup Brush Cleaner / It&#39;s Demo x Missha M Magic Cushion #23 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daiso and It&#39;s Demo are two completely different stores. Daiso makes all other dollar stores I&#39;ve been to look obsolete. While It&#39;s Demo gave me vibes Claire&#39;s in the US might have given me. Except less middle school girls running around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mission at Daiso was to get my hands on the famous makeup brush cleaner that&#39;s always out of stock. I managed to get enough bottles to last me a while. On first use it left my makeup brushes squeaky clean. And at around 90 cents a bottle, you can&#39;t go wrong. In the same aisle I found some gorgeous and natural looking lashes. I stocked up on those as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was an image that was surfacing around in the Asian beauty Instagram world. It was a picture of the cult classic Missha Cushion foundation with a limited edition Pokemon case. That&#39;s the only thing I walked into It&#39;s Demo for. I had to get my hands on it. First of all, the foundation itself is great on my skin and I ran out of it months back. Plus the packaging...I mean, COMMON, it&#39;s adorable. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;!-- Korea --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Korea&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My husband and I did a quick little visit to Seoul once again to shop ‘till we dropped. I ended up with old favorites and made some new discoveries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Innisfree --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Innisfree&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/innisfree.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt; Innisfree It&#39;s Real Squeeze Masks / Innisfree Ampoule Moisture Cushion #23 / Innisfree Skinny Microcara / Innisfree Waterproof Skinny Microcara / Innisfree Auto Eyebrow Pencil /
Innisfree Jeju Scent Picker Candle Set
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your girl right here is a DIE HARD FAN of Innisfree. I grabbed a basket and just started filling it up as soon as I walked into the door. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The face masks themselves are ok. They&#39;re very thin so it makes absorption to the skin quickly but I also ripped part of it by mistake just trying to get it out of the pouch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I live for the eyebrow pencils. They are smooth and make putting on my eyebrows in the morning a breeze. One pencil can last me up to 3 months! And I do my eyebrows almost every single day. It took everything in me to not get a lifetime supply all at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/innisfree_cushion.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My go-to winter cushion is the Ampule foundation from Innisfree. They had a 1 + 1 deal so of course, I put that in my basket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The skinny mascara line is quite good. I like the original formula but also added in the waterproof one for good measure. The tiny wand gets all the mascara fibers into every single eyelash. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I almost didn&#39;t get the candle collection until my husband snuck up behind me and mentioned I should just get them. I&#39;m glad I did. They smell amazing and look great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Olive Young --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Olive Young&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/olive_young.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
Clio Tinted Tattoo Kill Brow / Clio Tattoo Lasting Gel Pencil / Clio Kill Cover Foundation #4 Ginger
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Olive Young was having wild deals store wide when I was there. I picked up a Clio foundation set on sale. It comes with the cushion foundation, a foundation refill as well as a primer.  I also came across some really good eyebrow products. My eyebrows stay in place when I use a combination of the two. Clio has some of my favorite Korean beauty products I&#39;ve tried, these were no exception.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Skinfood --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skinfood&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/skinfood.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
 Skinfood Yuja Water Serum / Skinfood Gold Caviar Collagen Serum / Skinfood Nail Vita Nut Strengthener / Skinfood Nail Vita Pineapple Cuticle Cleaner / Skinfood Pine Nut Cuticle Oil / Skinfood Peach Cotton Pore Pact / Skinfood Mini Eyebrow Tools
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We keep a giant tub of yuja tea in the fidge at my place. When I saw that Skinfood carried and entire yuja line, I couldn&#39;t wait to try it. I got the yuja serum and it smells amazing. I use it in the morning and night for an extra boost of hydration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The gold caviar serum was mostly for my husband. He was in the market for night time skincare and he went with this as a serum option. More often than not, I reach out for this too. Can&#39;t help it. It smells wonderful and has little gold flecks so it feels ultra luxurious. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My nail beds tend to be weak and brittle but ever since I started using the nail strengthener, cuticle cleaner and oil I saw a change. My nails look and feel healthier. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/skinfood_pact.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently ran out of my peach compact and couldn&#39;t wait to get my hands on another one. It keeps the oil at bay during my work day and is small enough to throw in my makeup bag without taking up too much space. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m always keeping an eye out for small, portable tools that makes doing my eyebrows easier. These two little babies do the job so well! I can really blend out the edges and shape my brows with ease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Nature Republic --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nature Republic&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/nature_republic.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
 Nature Republic Hand &amp;amp; Nature Sanitizer Gel / Nature Republic Hand &amp;amp; Nature Sanitizer Hand Cream
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use both of these products every single day. I made sure to stock up for the entire year because these are my lifeline, particularly during flu season. If you&#39;re looking for a good sanitizer/hand cream duo, this is it! Plus the scents are subtle and not overwhelming like most western brands.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- MAC --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;MAC&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/mac_2.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
MAC x Steve J. &amp;amp; Yoni P. Lipstick in Spotlight Me
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only thing I picked up at the MAC store in Korea was a lipstick. The most perfect shade of peachy nude I&#39;ve ever seen.  It&#39;s called Spotlight Me and it&#39;s from the MAC collaboration with Korean Designers Steve J and Yoni P. The products on this line were meant to showcase &quot;Seoul street style made easy...&quot;. I know this collection was released globally but getting my hands on it in Seoul made it feel really special. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Korea --&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Birthday Haul&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Treat yo’ self.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- CVS --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CVS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/cvs.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
Peach Slices Acne Spot Dots / The Saem Saemmul Wrapping Tint in PK01 / Wet + Wild Perfect Pout Gel Lip Liner in Think Flamingos / Peach Slices Face Masks

&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can we talk about the Peach &amp;amp; Lily Peach Slices x CVS collection really quick? IT&#39;S LIFE CHANGING. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.peachandlily.com/pages/peach-slices-where-to-buy&quot;&gt;Go to your nearest CVS and stock up&lt;/a&gt;. The products are totally cute and at an excellent price point. I&#39;m so excited to see K-beauty become more accessible to everyone. There&#39;s a certain sense of comfort I get knowing I can pick up cold medicine, Doritos, and k-beauty products at the CVS next door. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got some acne right on my chin and have been using the Peach Slices Acne Spot Dots to calm down the redness, soak up any excess sebum and get my skin back on track. I will definitely be getting more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/peach_slices_masks.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Peach Slices sheet masks are a pretty good quality for less than $3 each. The packaging is so cute too!  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peel-off tints have been really popular on social media and I&#39;ve been wanting to try them myself. The Saem Wrapping Tint can be a little messy to use at first but once you peel off the tinted gel, THAT COLOR PAYOFF THO! I like using it as a base for the rest of my lip products. But it can definitely be used on its own. The default color is a beautiful rose shade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Wet N&#39; Wild lip liner is the perfect companion to the MAC lipstick mentioned above. It&#39;s almost a dupe, to be honest. I&#39;m so happy I picked this up on a whim.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Sephora --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sephora&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/sephora.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
Clinique Shadow Palette in Wear Everywhere Nudes / Yves Saint Laurent Volupté Tint-In-Oil in Cherry My Cherie / Supergoop! Defense Refresh Setting Mist SPF 50 / GLAMGLOW SUPERCLEANSE Daily Clearing Cleanser / GLAMGLOW SUPERMUD Clearing Treatment / Christophe Robin Cleansing Purifying Scrub with Sea Salt / Elizabeth and James Nirvana White / Buxom Plumpline Lip Liner in Hush Hush

&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt; I had my eyes on the YSL tint for a while now. I got it as part of a mini sample 500 point YSL kit at Sephora a long time ago but since it was my birthday month, why not splurge on the full size? It leaves lips looking juicy and supple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Supergoop setting SPF spray is something that I was on the hunt for. I wanted something that would help me reapply SPF in the middle of the day without having to use actual sunscreen and ruin my makeup. Shout out the amazing &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/natch-beaut/id1223715132?mt=2&quot;&gt;podcast&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/NatchBeaut/?fref=nf&quot;&gt;beauty community&lt;/a&gt; of Natch Beaut! They suggested this setting spray and it&#39;s just what I was looking for. I would not use this by itself as the only source of sunscreen and a setting spray. It does have its flaws but for reapplying SPF between my commute from the office to straight home, it&#39;s just the thing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/eyeshadow.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clinique eyeshadows were the first eyeshadows I ever owned. Why did I leave them? THEY ARE GREAT. I really wanted an everyday palette and this one looks so promising. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My skin has been acting up lately. But GLAMGLOW TO THE RESCUE. I&#39;ve had great success with the clearing treatment mask, I&#39;m hoping the cleanser also proves to be a good product to keep in my arsenal against acne. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Needed a new scent for summer and got the Elizabeth and James Nirvana White perfume. The hype is real. It&#39;s a luxurious scent. The rollerball is perfect to throw on a makeup bag and go!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/shampoo.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my oily haired babes, the Christophe Robin Cleansing Shampoo is the BEST SHAMPOO I&#39;VE USED FOR MY OILY HAIR. PERIOD. Try this out! Got a sample of this in a Sephora Play box a couple of months back and I was so impressed how clean and lightweight my hair felt. I knew I need to go buy a bigger size. I use it once a week as a treatment. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The almighty K-Beauty queen, PONY, used a Buxom lippie in the shade &quot;Hush Hush&quot; in one of her tutorials recently and I had to get my hands on it. It&#39;s an awesome &quot;my lip color, but better&quot; shade. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;!-- Gentle Monster --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gentle Monster&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/gentle_monster.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
Gentle Monster Glasses in Samo 
&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hubby came thru and surprised me with the cutest little frames from Gentle Monster. I was in need of a new pair of glasses. I&#39;m so excited to be adding these to my Gentle Monster collection. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Madewell --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Madewell&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/madewell.JPG&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Products above&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
Madewell Leather Pouch Wallet / Madewell Marfa bag
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wallet had a rough time keeping up with currency exchange on my honeymoon. I rarely use cash so having spare change, bills, subway cards, and random tickets on top of what I was already carrying popped the zipper on my old wallet. I desperately needed an upgrade. This simple wallet from Madewell can fit so much! When I was getting the wallet my eyes also wondered to a beautiful circular bag I wanted in my life. Perfect combo! 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WOOOOO, ok. Haul complete. What have you&#39;ve splurged on recently? Let me know in the comments below. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
  (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i[&#39;GoogleAnalyticsObject&#39;]=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
  (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
  m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
  })(window,document,&#39;script&#39;,&#39;https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js&#39;,&#39;ga&#39;);

  ga(&#39;create&#39;, &#39;UA-87732213-1&#39;, &#39;auto&#39;);
  ga(&#39;send&#39;, &#39;pageview&#39;);

&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2017/07/03/japan-korea-birthday-hauls.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2017/07/03/japan-korea-birthday-hauls.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Survive a Long Haul Flight</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/travel.jpg&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;auto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year I took my first ever 14-hour flight from New York City to Seoul. I greatly underestimated how slow time seems to move up in the air. Since I’m right in the middle of planning another trip with a long haul flight, I figured I’d share my tips and tricks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;1. Pick your airline and seat accordingly&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Being well prepared for your long flight starts from the second you buy those plane tickets. I am constantly on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.skyscanner.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Skyscanner&lt;/a&gt; to check out flight deals. I also make sure to have a tab open on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.airlinequality.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Skytrax&lt;/a&gt; for airline reviews. Some foreign airlines have perks in economy class. We&#39;re talking slippers, toothbrush sets, the kind of stuff you usually find in business class. Depending on what airline you pick and what aircraft they use for your specific flight, the seat layout can be different. Be sure to check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.seatguru.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;SeatGuru&lt;/a&gt; to make sure you&#39;re getting that seat you want! #TeamAisleSeat  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;2. Pack like a pro&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Packing your carry-on is easy. There are plenty of tutorials online showing how to pack two weeks worth of clothes in a tiny 18 inch suitcse. It&#39;s your personal item, the one that is usually stored under your seat, that is key to maintaining sanity during a long flight. My personal item is usually a tote bag that I stuff with:   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Ear plugs&lt;br /&gt;
Eye mask&lt;br /&gt;
Travel Pillow (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004ZIKWJW/ref=twister_B01M32OMAM?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;psc=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Best $40 I&#39;ve ever spent&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;
Blanket scarf&lt;br /&gt;
Toiletries bag&lt;br /&gt;
Baby Wipes&lt;br /&gt;
Pen (for filling out those international slips)&lt;br /&gt;
Entertainment&lt;br /&gt;
Charger (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/BESTEK-Voltage-Converter-Travel-Adapter/dp/B012ERZ7B8/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1487630934&amp;amp;sr=8-1-spons&amp;amp;keywords=voltage+converter&amp;amp;psc=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;international adaptors/converter too since some planes won&#39;t carry US voltage&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;
Snacks&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;3. BYOS: bring your own snacks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
My experience with food on long flights has been mixed. I loved the Bibimbap lunch from Asiana Airlines (Go ahead, judge me). But there were also some questionable food options too. (Burritos in a box anyone?) I usually pack a little paper lunch bag of snacks that will hold up well in a long flight. Trail mix, freeze dried fruit, chips, a granola bar and an instant cup noodle for something in between meal times (Just kindly ask your flight attendant for hot water). Remember that you still need to abide by the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tsa.gov/travel/security-screening/prohibited-items&quot;&gt;TSA guidelines&lt;/a&gt;. So don&#39;t bring an enrite meal with you.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;4. Flight attendants are your BFFs&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It&#39;s hard to keep it together as a traveler when you didn&#39;t sleep well the night before, you&#39;re stuck on Terminal 4 with other restless passengers, and you really wished you had eaten a salad instead of the Shake Shack you inhaled before you found out your flight was delayed. But there is no excuse to take your feelings out on the staff. Let me explain. Once that flight is boarded, flight attendants are your life support! You don&#39;t want to get off on the wrong foot with them, especially since you&#39;ll be seeing them constantly for all of the flight. Remember that the same rules of courtesy and respect that apply on the ground, apply in the air as well. And if you want to go the extra mile, bring a little chocolate for them. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;5. Bring entertainment, A LOT OF IT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
You don&#39;t want to rely on the VOD on the plane or whatever the Hudson News stall is selling to get you through 14 hours. Bring a good book. Download all the podcast episodes you can. Download those movies and shows you&#39;re been meaning to watch on your laptop or tablet. While you&#39;re at it, download all your favorite songs too. I&#39;M TALKING HOURS OF ENTERTAINMENT HERE!!! If you&#39;re like me, you&#39;ve been training for this moment since you got a Netflix account. This is the time to binge watch guilt free.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;6. Hydrate and stretch &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Being in a tin can full of recycled air for hours on end can make you feel miserable. Your skin starts to get dry, your nose and sinuses feel terrible and the neck pains kick in at around hour four of the flight. Make sure you stay hydrated with plenty of water and tea. Knock back an Airborne if you can. Take a little stroll through the ailes before headed to the bathroom. Stay healthy my friends. You don&#39;t want a cold that you cought on the airplane to ruin a vacation. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
You got any tips and tricks for me? I&#39;d love to hear them.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
  (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i[&#39;GoogleAnalyticsObject&#39;]=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
  (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
  m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
  })(window,document,&#39;script&#39;,&#39;https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js&#39;,&#39;ga&#39;);

  ga(&#39;create&#39;, &#39;UA-87732213-1&#39;, &#39;auto&#39;);
  ga(&#39;send&#39;, &#39;pageview&#39;);

&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2017/02/20/how-to-survive-long-flight.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2017/02/20/how-to-survive-long-flight.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hall of Faves: Twenty-Sixteen</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Twenty-sixteen was insane. But I made some discoveries along the way that helped me navigate this crazy year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Music&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tomppabeats&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Harbor&lt;br /&gt;
Favorite song: The Girl Next Door&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://embed.spotify.com/?uri=spotify%3Aalbum%3A217LLrb47lzGE3HANjBLnn&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br /&gt;


Tomppabeats has been the soundtrack to my life at home in 2016. &quot;Harbor&quot; is on the Sonos from the time I wake up to the time I go to bed. Every song on this album clocks in at a minute or less. They&#39;re like little nuggets of beats.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dean&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
130 Mood : TRBL&lt;br /&gt;
Favorite song: 21&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://embed.spotify.com/?uri=spotify%3Aalbum%3A1MW3txTS49ZGvyLi0fziLU&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br /&gt;


As soon as I was in the air and en route to Seoul this spring, Dean&#39;s music was EVERYWHERE. He was on the VOD on the airplane, cat cafes, shopping centers... you name it. I hadn&#39;t listened to Korean music since I was in middle school, but he made me take the plunge again. I was lucky enough to see him live in NYC in June, it was well worth the road trip!  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Crush&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Interlude - EP&lt;br /&gt;
Favorite song: 먼지 (Dust)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://embed.spotify.com/?uri=spotify%3Aalbum%3A2f9Pae8JWuf6kKpNhfOf8a&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br /&gt;


Crush is another Korean musician on my list.  The &quot;Interlude&quot; EP is one of the best I&#39;ve heard all year. Sultry sounds? Check. Great production? Check. Songs I can turn up in the car to? CHECK! I also took the trip to NYC to see him live and it was my favorite concert of the year. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;TV&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stranger Things&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/strangerthings.gif&quot; height=&quot;100%&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What could I write about this that hasn’t been said already? Stranger Things is binge watching at it’s finest. It was the best thing I’ve seen all summer. Every hour was a thrill ride. And the soundtrack was badass. I’m excited to see where they take us in season two.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;She Was Pretty&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/shewaspretty.gif&quot; height=&quot;100%&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order for us to passively pick up some Korean before our vacation, Vincent and I binged watched a lot of K-dramas. She Was Pretty was our favorite. This drama is about childhood crushes losing touch after many years but reuniting under the strangest of circumstances. There’s also nothing like a good love triangle to keep me on edge. This drama is so good it got syndicated to Latin America which is how my mom got wind of it. She loved it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Literally anything on Viceland&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/vicelandphone.gif&quot; height=&quot;100%&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Viceland came into my life via the cable box and I am so thankful. Finally a channel I can leave on all day and there’s quality programming every single hour. Favorite shows include Noisy, Huang’s world, Deadset on Life and Desus &amp;amp; Mero.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Podcasts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bodega Boys&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/298257001&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=false&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&quot; style=&quot;margin-left:40px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Desus and Mero, before they had their show on Viceland, I was cracking up at every single episode of their podcast, Bodega Boys. Hilarious commentary on politics, sports, pop culture and life in the Bronx. Gonna want to grab your headphones for this one: NSFW. #bodegahive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;This Week Had Me Like&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/294871309&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=false&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&quot; style=&quot;margin-left:40px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This podcast is 600 level college course on pop culture. Caroline covers topics from Stevie Wonder blind truthers, Dr. Drew’s potential singing career, Alyssa Milano’s paper towel collection and that’s not even scratching the surface. Each episode is well curated to bring you the most obscure celebrity news you can’t find anywhere else. I wish this podcast was weekly because I can not get enough. Also NSFW.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who? Weekly&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/264347583&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=false&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&quot; style=&quot;margin-left:40px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t tell you how many times I’ve been in the grocery store line and seen a tabloid headline featuring a celebrity I don’t know, let alone care for. This is where Who? Weekly comes in. This twice a week podcast helps you go from “Wait, who?” to “Oh, her” with every episode. Thanks to this podcast, I probably know more about Rita Ora than I do my own self. You can find Who? Weekly on iTunes. (Ok, maybe all the podcasts I enjoy are NSFW.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
  (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i[&#39;GoogleAnalyticsObject&#39;]=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
  (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
  m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
  })(window,document,&#39;script&#39;,&#39;https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js&#39;,&#39;ga&#39;);

  ga(&#39;create&#39;, &#39;UA-87732213-1&#39;, &#39;auto&#39;);
  ga(&#39;send&#39;, &#39;pageview&#39;);

&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2016/12/12/hall-of-faves-2016.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2016/12/12/hall-of-faves-2016.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
